Contact

gibsonc4@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dr-christy-gibson-dnp-aprn-fnp-c-ccrn-wcc-7a3506150 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care

Nursing

Clinical Research

Certifications

Wound Care Certified
Critical Care Registered Nurse
Family Nurse Practitioner

Honors-Awards
Honor Society of Nursing

Dr. Christy Gibson, DNP, APRN, FNP-C, CCRN, WCC

Doctorate of Nursing Practice

Senoia, Georgia

Summary

Experienced Clinical Director with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Family Practice Medicine, and Healthcare Management. Strong healthcare services professional with a Doctorate in Nursing Practice from Troy University.

Experience

Resurgia Health Solutions
Director of Advanced Clinical Providers
February 2016 - Present (4 years 4 months)

Premier Immediate Care of Georgia Family Nurse Practitioner, Urgent Care July 2015 - May 2016 (11 months) Lawrenceville, GA

PRN position

Troy University
Clinical Adjunct Faculty for FNP Program
August 2011 - May 2016 (4 years 10 months)
Greater Atlanta Area

Healthcare Clinic at Walgreens Clinic Manager September 2014 - February 2016 (1 year 6 months) Newnan, Carrollton, Peachtree City GA

Piedmont Healthcare
Clinical Manager
July 2012 - September 2014 (2 years 3 months)

Fayetteville, Georiga

Clinical Manager of Orthopedics
Clinical Nurse Expert of Critical Care

East Alabama Medical Center Infectious Disease Nurse Practitioner July 2006 - July 2012 (6 years 1 month) Opelika, AL

Infectious Disease Nurse Practitioner Charge Nurse Intensive Care Unit

Education

Troy University

Doctorate of Nursing Practice, Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Troy University

Master of Science in Nursing, Family Nurse Practitioner · (2009 - 2011)

Troy University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2007 - 2009)

Southern Union Community College

Associate of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1999 - 2001)